<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Girlguiding Beeston and Chilwell</title>
    <link>http://samozzy.github.io/guides/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content on Girlguiding Beeston and Chilwell</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2016 Girlguiding</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2016 15:40:05 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://samozzy.github.io/guides/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Adults in Girlguiding</title>
      <link>http://samozzy.github.io/guides/adults/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2016 15:40:05 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://samozzy.github.io/guides/adults/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;adults&#34;&gt;Adults&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Girlguiding UK isn&amp;rsquo;t just for girls. In Beeston and Chilwell Division, we have around 160 adult volunteers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whatever level of commitment you can make - from ocassional &amp;lsquo;behind-the-scenes&amp;rsquo; support, to planning and leading activities every week - we&amp;rsquo;d love to have you on the team. In return for your time, we offer training and the opportunity to develop new skills.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are many volunteer roles in guiding. Many volunteers give their time as Leaders or Assistant Leaders for guiding units and get to see girls enjoying events and activities that they have organised. Other volunteers take on administrative responsibilities, or help out with driving or maintenance on an occasional basis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Being a Leader gave me the confidence to get back out to work – I initially signed up to do it every other week. Now I&amp;rsquo;m thinking of retraining and working with children!&amp;rdquo; &lt;small&gt;Pamela&lt;/small&gt;
&amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s been fantastic sharing all the experiences and laughs with some close personal friends.&amp;rdquo; &lt;small&gt;Liz&lt;/small&gt;
&amp;ldquo;As Leaders we learn marketing, leadership and communication skills and about fundraising, programme planning and teamwork. These are transferable skills which are extremely valuable in the workplace.&amp;rdquo; &lt;small&gt;Nina&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;volunteers&#34;&gt;Volunteers&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;

  
  
      
    
      
    
  
  
  
   
  
   

   
  
 	&lt;p class=&#34;pullquote pullquote-center&#34; data-pullquote=&#34;Volunteers make Guiding happen! Do something extraordinary!&#34;&gt;
 	&lt;hr class=&#34;pullquote-center&#34;&gt;
  	 
	&lt;/p&gt;
  


Could you help girls and young women to develop their potential? Girlguiding values all its leaders and helpers - and the girls do too! This is hardly surprising when you consider what our volunteers get up to.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have a whole range of roles available to suit you no matter how much time or what skills you can offer. Flexible volunteering makes it easy for people to share skills, time and energy in a way that suits their lifestyle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These roles can include:
&lt;div class=&#34;row&#34;&gt;
	


 
  
	
		&lt;div class=&#34;col-sm-6&#34;&gt; 
			&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Becoming a leader and attending regular meetings.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Supporting leaders as an occasional unit helper.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Organizing safe, interesting activities inspired by the ideas of girls and young women, encouraging them to have a voice.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Taking girls and young women on residential trips, such as sleepovers, camping and outdoor adventures including climbing, canoeing and abseiling.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

		&lt;/div&gt;




 
  
	
		&lt;div class=&#34;col-sm-6&#34;&gt; 
			&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enabling girls and young women to learn new skills in a unique girl-only space.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Running websites, refreshment stalls, shopping online.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Managing funds and helping make best use of resources.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assisting with admin related tasks.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

		&lt;/div&gt;



&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;what-s-in-it-for-you&#34;&gt;What&amp;rsquo;s in it for you?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a volunteer with Girlguiding, you&amp;rsquo;ll make new friends, have a good time and make a real difference to the lives of today&amp;rsquo;s girls and young women. You will also develop skills that will look great on your CV, including leadership, team working and communication.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As well as broadening the horizons of girls and young women aged between 5 years and 25 years old it also gives you a chance to broaden your own horizons.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;what-are-we-looking-for&#34;&gt;What are we looking for?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Enthusiasm, common sense and a friendly approach are all that’s needed really. As a volunteer you will get a great sense of satisfaction from watching the girls and young women develop their confidence and skills, as well as have lots of fun.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Training and support is given to new volunteers as they work within their Unit. DBS checks will be necessary. This is paid for by Girlguiding. We are happy to explore ways of flexible volunteering.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a volunteer you’ll also gain from the experience by making new friends and learning new skills such as leadership and organisational abilities that you can use at work or put on a CV.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Volunteers make Guiding happen! Be part of it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;trefoil-guild&#34;&gt;Trefoil Guild&lt;/h1&gt;



  
  
      
    
      
    
  
  
  
   
  
   

   
  
 	&lt;p class=&#34;pullquote pullquote-center&#34; data-pullquote=&#34;Sharing your skills, experience, wisdom, nurturing the young – keeping the fun and adventure of Guiding alive.&#34;&gt;
 	&lt;hr class=&#34;pullquote-center&#34;&gt;
  	The Trefoil Guild offers a warm welcome to everyone, male or female, aged 18 or over, whether or not they have previously been connected with the Guide Movement.&lt;br /&gt;
Full membership is open to anyone willing to make or renew the Guide/Scout promise and affiliated membership to those who don’t wish to do so provided they subscribe to the aims and principles of Girlguiding. There is also associate membership for any adult still active in the Guide/Scout Association. 
	&lt;/p&gt;
  



&lt;div class=&#34;row&#34;&gt;
	


 
  
	
		&lt;div class=&#34;col-sm-6&#34;&gt; 
			&lt;h3 id=&#34;aims&#34;&gt;Aims:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To live in the spirit of Guiding&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To offer practical help to Girlguiding&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To support Guiding worldwide&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To carry the spirit of Guiding &amp;amp; Scouting into the communities where we live&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

		&lt;/div&gt;




 
  
	
		&lt;div class=&#34;col-sm-6&#34;&gt; 
			Many Guild activities result in positive benefit to the community, but as any Guild member will tell you, a large part of the programme is devoted to having plain old-fashioned fun!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a Division we are very fortunate to have an active Trefoil Guild to support us.
		&lt;/div&gt;



&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The group meets monthly on the 4th Wednesday of each month (except December when it is 2nd Wednesday) and there are currently 31 members in the group.  As well as having speakers at their monthly meetings the group regularly raises money for charities, visits places of interest, meets up with other Trefoil Guilds and helps out with Division and County events.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1</title>
      <link>http://samozzy.github.io/guides/homepage/1%20-%20Intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2016 00:02:48 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://samozzy.github.io/guides/homepage/1%20-%20Intro/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;text-center&#34;&gt;
 &lt;h1 id=&#34;girlguiding-opens-a-world-of-opportunities-that-will-last-a-lifetime&#34;&gt;Girlguiding opens a world of opportunities that will last a lifetime&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beeston and Chilwell Division has over 650 members across 15 groups across all of Beeston and Chilwell. Our members are of all ages, spanning our Rainbows, Brownies, Guides, Senior Section and adult volunteers - including many students from the University of Nottingham.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Being a member of Girlguiding opens a world of opportunities that will last a lifetime. It provides a safe, girl-only space to explore activities, issues and possibilities that are available to girls today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are a friendly, forward looking division and our aim is to provide the best guiding and life opportunities for all our members. This is made possible by the enthusiasm and efforts of our many volunteers – no contribution is too small.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5</title>
      <link>http://samozzy.github.io/guides/homepage/5%20-%20Volunteers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2016 23:50:01 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://samozzy.github.io/guides/homepage/5%20-%20Volunteers/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;volunteers-make-guiding-happen&#34;&gt;Volunteers make Guiding happen&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Enthusiasm, common sense and a friendly approach are all that’s needed. As a volunteer with Girlguiding, you&amp;rsquo;ll make new friends, have a good time and make a real difference to the lives of today&amp;rsquo;s girls and young women. Beeston and Chilwell Division Rainbows, Brownies and Guides need you! Lots of girls are waiting but we need leaders and helpers to get them in on all the fun.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Opportunities exist on different evenings throughout Beeston and Chilwell, with full support and training available. Flexible volunteering makes it easy for people to share skills, time and energy in a way that suits their lifestyle.&lt;/p&gt;


 

	 
	
		
	
		
	
		
	
		
			&lt;div class=&#34;row text-left&#34;&gt; 
				&lt;div class=&#34;col-md-8 col-md-offset-2 col-xs-12&#34;&gt;
					&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;h3&gt;After studying English at university, I decided I wanted to teach. My experience within guiding helped me to gain a place on one of the best teaching courses and now I am teaching English to Guide age and above! &lt;small&gt;Komal, Girlguiding Beeston Leader&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
				&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
		
	

</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4</title>
      <link>http://samozzy.github.io/guides/homepage/4%20-%20Adults/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2016 23:49:45 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://samozzy.github.io/guides/homepage/4%20-%20Adults/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;adults&#34;&gt;Adults&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Girlguiding isn&amp;rsquo;t just for girls - within Beeston and Chilwell Division, there are over 160 adult volunteers. Many amazing volunteers contribute time to guiding every year. In return, we offer training and the opportunity to develop new skills.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are many volunteer roles in guiding. Many volunteers give their time as Leaders or Assistant Leaders for guiding units and get to see girls enjoying events and activities that they have organised. Other volunteers take on administrative responsibilities, or help out with driving or maintenance on an occasional basis.&lt;/p&gt;


 

	 
	
		
	
		
	
		
			&lt;div class=&#34;row text-left&#34;&gt; 
				&lt;div class=&#34;col-md-8 col-md-offset-2 col-xs-12&#34;&gt;
					&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Guiding has helped me become the person I am today, which is a confident and outspoken girl! &lt;small&gt;Dawn, 17&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
				&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
		
	
		
	

</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2</title>
      <link>http://samozzy.github.io/guides/homepage/2%20-%20We%20Do/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2016 20:00:51 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://samozzy.github.io/guides/homepage/2%20-%20We%20Do/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;row&#34;&gt;
	


 
  
	
		&lt;div class=&#34;col-sm-4&#34;&gt; 
			&lt;h2 id=&#34;we-provide-girls-their-own-space&#34;&gt;We provide girls their own space&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We give girls a place where they can really be themselves with other girls and share the experience of growing up as a girl in today’s world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We provide a safe, non-judgemental environment where girls can explore the issues they care about while having lots of fun, enjoying new experiences and learning vital skills.
		&lt;/div&gt;




 
  
	
		&lt;div class=&#34;col-sm-4&#34;&gt; 
			&lt;h2 id=&#34;we-are-for-all-girls&#34;&gt;We are for all girls&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are for all girls and young women, whatever their background and circumstances. We offer them fun, exciting activities and the chance to make lifelong friends.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’ll find us in many communities, helping to give girls a head start in life and encouraging them to be happy, self-confident and curious about the world they live in and the difference they can make.
		&lt;/div&gt;




 
  
	
		&lt;div class=&#34;col-sm-4&#34;&gt; 
			&lt;h2 id=&#34;we-give-girls-a-voice&#34;&gt;We give girls a voice&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We give girls the confidence, skills and information to make informed decisions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We offer a supportive, inclusive and exciting environment where they can reach their own conclusions about the world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We show them how they can speak out and take positive action to improve their lives and the lives of others.
		&lt;/div&gt;



&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
 

	 
	
		
			&lt;div class=&#34;row text-left&#34;&gt; 
				&lt;div class=&#34;col-md-8 col-md-offset-2 col-xs-12&#34;&gt;
					&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;h3&gt;We play games, we celebrate things, we write in our books, we play on the computer, we do painting… &lt;small&gt;Fareeha, 6&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
				&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
		
	
		
	
		
	
		
	
&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3</title>
      <link>http://samozzy.github.io/guides/homepage/3%20-%20Our%20Groups/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2016 20:00:51 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://samozzy.github.io/guides/homepage/3%20-%20Our%20Groups/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;our-groups&#34;&gt;Our groups&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
 

	 
	
	   
	    &lt;div class=&#34;col-md-3 col-sm-6&#34;&gt;
	      &lt;h3&gt;Rainbows&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://samozzy.github.io/guides/guides/groups/#rainbows&#39;&gt;&lt;button class=&#34;btn btn-primary&#34;&gt;Read more...&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
	      &lt;p&gt;Girlguiding starts aged 5 with our youngest group. Rainbows play games, have parties, make things and enjoy the outdoors while developing life skills.&lt;/p&gt;
	    &lt;/div&gt;
	  
  


 

	 
	
	   
	    &lt;div class=&#34;col-md-3 col-sm-6&#34;&gt;
	      &lt;h3&gt;Brownies&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://samozzy.github.io/guides/guides/groups/#brownies&#39;&gt;&lt;button class=&#34;btn btn-primary&#34;&gt;Read more...&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
	      &lt;p&gt;Brownies do it all! From ages 7-10, Brownies make up and take on their own challenges, as well as playing fun games.&lt;/p&gt;
	    &lt;/div&gt;
	  
  


 

	 
	
	   
	    &lt;div class=&#34;col-md-3 col-sm-6&#34;&gt;
	      &lt;h3&gt;Guides&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://samozzy.github.io/guides/guides/groups/#guides&#39;&gt;&lt;button class=&#34;btn btn-primary&#34;&gt;Read more...&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
	      &lt;p&gt;Being a Guide encourages girls aged 10-14 to develop by undertaking challenges and pushing the boundaries of their experience.&lt;/p&gt;
	    &lt;/div&gt;
	  
  


 

	 
	
	   
	    &lt;div class=&#34;col-md-3 col-sm-6&#34;&gt;
	      &lt;h3&gt;Senior Section&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://samozzy.github.io/guides/guides/groups/#senior-section&#39;&gt;&lt;button class=&#34;btn btn-primary&#34;&gt;Read more...&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
	      &lt;p&gt;For anyone 14-25, the Senior Section offers young women an exciting and flexible programme with a huge variety of challenges and opportunities for personal development.&lt;/p&gt;
	    &lt;/div&gt;
	  
  
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
 

	 
	
		
	
		
			&lt;div class=&#34;row text-left&#34;&gt; 
				&lt;div class=&#34;col-md-8 col-md-offset-2 col-xs-12&#34;&gt;
					&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;h3&gt;It feels nice to be part of a group of girls who help each other and are friendly. It makes me feel special. I&amp;#39;d hate there to be boys at Brownies! &lt;small&gt;Heather, 10&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
				&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
		
	
		
	
		
	
&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meet the Team</title>
      <link>http://samozzy.github.io/guides/team/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2016 22:16:24 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://samozzy.github.io/guides/team/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;executive&#34;&gt;Executive&lt;/h2&gt;


 

	 

	 
		
		
			
		
		 
		&lt;div class=&#34;row&#34;&gt;
			
				

				&lt;div class=&#34;col-md-6 col-sm-6 text-center&#34; &gt;
					
						&lt;img class=&#34;img-circle&#34; src=&#34;../img/branding/trefoil.png&#34; alt=&#34;Kelly Congreave&#34; title=&#34;Kelly Congreave&#34; height=100 /&gt;
					
					&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kelly Congreave&lt;/strong&gt;
					&lt;br /&gt;Division Administrator
					
						&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;mailto:kellycongreave@aol.com&#34; title=&#34;kellycongreave@aol.com&#34; alt=&#34;kellycongreave@aol.com&#34;&gt;
							&lt;small&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;fa fa-envelope&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt; kellycongreave@aol.com&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
					
					&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;/div&gt;
			
				

				&lt;div class=&#34;col-md-6 col-sm-6 text-center&#34; &gt;
					
						&lt;img class=&#34;img-circle&#34; src=&#34;../img/branding/trefoil.png&#34; alt=&#34;Kaye Ford&#34; title=&#34;Kaye Ford&#34; height=100 /&gt;
					
					&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kaye Ford&lt;/strong&gt;
					&lt;br /&gt;Treasurer
					
						&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;mailto:kayeford@hotmail.co.uk&#34; title=&#34;kayeford@hotmail.co.uk&#34; alt=&#34;kayeford@hotmail.co.uk&#34;&gt;
							&lt;small&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;fa fa-envelope&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt; kayeford@hotmail.co.uk&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
					
					&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;/div&gt;
			
		&lt;/div&gt;
	



&lt;h2 id=&#34;beeston-team&#34;&gt;Beeston Team&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
 

	 

	 
		
		
			 
		
		 
		&lt;div class=&#34;row&#34;&gt;
			
				

				&lt;div class=&#34;col-md-4 col-sm-6 text-center&#34; &gt;
					
						&lt;img class=&#34;img-circle&#34; src=&#34;../img/branding/trefoil.png&#34; alt=&#34;Helen Sladen&#34; title=&#34;Helen Sladen&#34; height=100 /&gt;
					
					&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Helen Sladen&lt;/strong&gt;
					&lt;br /&gt;District Commissioner
					
						&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;mailto:beestondistrict@gmail.com&#34; title=&#34;beestondistrict@gmail.com&#34; alt=&#34;beestondistrict@gmail.com&#34;&gt;
							&lt;small&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;fa fa-envelope&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt; beestondistrict@gmail.com&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
					
					&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;/div&gt;
			
				

				&lt;div class=&#34;col-md-4 col-sm-6 text-center&#34; &gt;
					
						&lt;img class=&#34;img-circle&#34; src=&#34;../img/branding/trefoil.png&#34; alt=&#34;Jacqui Walker&#34; title=&#34;Jacqui Walker&#34; height=100 /&gt;
					
					&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jacqui Walker&lt;/strong&gt;
					&lt;br /&gt;Assistant District Commissioner
					
					&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;/div&gt;
			
				
					&lt;div class=&#34;clearfix visible-sm-block&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt; 
				

				&lt;div class=&#34;col-md-4 col-sm-6 text-center&#34; &gt;
					
						&lt;img class=&#34;img-circle&#34; src=&#34;../img/branding/trefoil.png&#34; alt=&#34;Jenny Eyley&#34; title=&#34;Jenny Eyley&#34; height=100 /&gt;
					
					&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jenny Eyley&lt;/strong&gt;
					&lt;br /&gt;District Assistant Rainbows
					
					&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;/div&gt;
			
				 
					&lt;div class=&#34;clearfix visible-md-block visible-lg-block&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt; 
				

				&lt;div class=&#34;col-md-4 col-sm-6 text-center&#34; &gt;
					
						&lt;img class=&#34;img-circle&#34; src=&#34;../img/branding/trefoil.png&#34; alt=&#34;Mary Marinov&#34; title=&#34;Mary Marinov&#34; height=100 /&gt;
					
					&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mary Marinov&lt;/strong&gt;
					&lt;br /&gt;District Assistant Guide/Senior Section
					
					&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;/div&gt;
			
		&lt;/div&gt;
	

&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;chilwell-team&#34;&gt;Chilwell Team&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
 

	 

	 
		
		
			
		
		 
		&lt;div class=&#34;row&#34;&gt;
			
				

				&lt;div class=&#34;col-md-12 col-sm-6 text-center&#34; &gt;
					
						&lt;img class=&#34;img-circle&#34; src=&#34;../img/branding/trefoil.png&#34; alt=&#34;Sarah Priestland&#34; title=&#34;Sarah Priestland&#34; height=100 /&gt;
					
					&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sarah Priestland&lt;/strong&gt;
					&lt;br /&gt;Chilwell District Commissioner
					
					&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;/div&gt;
			
		&lt;/div&gt;
	

&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;our-advisors&#34;&gt;Our advisors&lt;/h2&gt;


 

	 

	 
		
		
			 
		
		 
		&lt;div class=&#34;row&#34;&gt;
			
				

				&lt;div class=&#34;col-md-4 col-sm-6 text-center&#34; &gt;
					
						&lt;img class=&#34;img-circle&#34; src=&#34;../img/branding/trefoil.png&#34; alt=&#34;Louise Lee&#34; title=&#34;Louise Lee&#34; height=100 /&gt;
					
					&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Louise Lee&lt;/strong&gt;
					&lt;br /&gt;Rainbow and Brownie Overnight Advisor
					
						&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;mailto:peter.lee@ntlworld.com&#34; title=&#34;peter.lee@ntlworld.com&#34; alt=&#34;peter.lee@ntlworld.com&#34;&gt;
							&lt;small&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;fa fa-envelope&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt; peter.lee@ntlworld.com&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
					
					&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;/div&gt;
			
				

				&lt;div class=&#34;col-md-4 col-sm-6 text-center&#34; &gt;
					
						&lt;img class=&#34;img-circle&#34; src=&#34;../img/branding/trefoil.png&#34; alt=&#34;Morag Dolby&#34; title=&#34;Morag Dolby&#34; height=100 /&gt;
					
					&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Morag Dolby&lt;/strong&gt;
					&lt;br /&gt;Guide and Senior Section Camp Advisor
					
						&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;mailto:m.dolby159@btinternet.com&#34; title=&#34;m.dolby159@btinternet.com&#34; alt=&#34;m.dolby159@btinternet.com&#34;&gt;
							&lt;small&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;fa fa-envelope&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt; m.dolby159@btinternet.com&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
					
					&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;/div&gt;
			
				
					&lt;div class=&#34;clearfix visible-sm-block&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt; 
				

				&lt;div class=&#34;col-md-4 col-sm-6 text-center&#34; &gt;
					
						&lt;img class=&#34;img-circle&#34; src=&#34;../img/branding/trefoil.png&#34; alt=&#34;Rebecca Scattergood&#34; title=&#34;Rebecca Scattergood&#34; height=100 /&gt;
					
					&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rebecca Scattergood&lt;/strong&gt;
					&lt;br /&gt;Senior Section Advisor
					
						&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;mailto:bexscattergood@aol.com&#34; title=&#34;bexscattergood@aol.com&#34; alt=&#34;bexscattergood@aol.com&#34;&gt;
							&lt;small&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;fa fa-envelope&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt; bexscattergood@aol.com&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
					
					&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;/div&gt;
			
				 
					&lt;div class=&#34;clearfix visible-md-block visible-lg-block&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt; 
				

				&lt;div class=&#34;col-md-4 col-sm-6 text-center&#34; &gt;
					
						&lt;img class=&#34;img-circle&#34; src=&#34;../img/branding/trefoil.png&#34; alt=&#34;Tonya Machin&#34; title=&#34;Tonya Machin&#34; height=100 /&gt;
					
					&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tonya Machin&lt;/strong&gt;
					&lt;br /&gt;Marketing and Communications Advisor
					
						&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;mailto:tonya.machin@ntlworld.com&#34; title=&#34;tonya.machin@ntlworld.com&#34; alt=&#34;tonya.machin@ntlworld.com&#34;&gt;
							&lt;small&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;fa fa-envelope&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt; tonya.machin@ntlworld.com&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
					
					&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;/div&gt;
			
		&lt;/div&gt;
	


</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Groups</title>
      <link>http://samozzy.github.io/guides/groups/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2016 01:17:01 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://samozzy.github.io/guides/groups/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;rainbows&#34;&gt;Rainbows&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;

  
  
      
    
      
    
  
  
  
   
  
   

   
  
 	&lt;p class=&#34;pullquote pullquote-center&#34; data-pullquote=&#34;Rainbows have fun!&#34;&gt;
 	&lt;hr class=&#34;pullquote-center&#34;&gt;
  	 
	&lt;/p&gt;
  


They play games, have parties, make things and enjoy the outdoors while developing life skills.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They follow a programme called the &lt;strong&gt;Rainbow Jigsaw&lt;/strong&gt;, which involves a wide range of activities and games. Being a Rainbow is all about learning, developing self-confidence, building friendships and, of course, having lots of fun!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Rainbow Jigsaw has four areas: &lt;em&gt;Look, Learn, Laugh, Love&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What do girls say about Rainbows?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;We play games, we celebrate things, we write in our books, we play on the computer, we do painting…&amp;rdquo; &lt;small&gt;Fareeha, 6&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;We&amp;rsquo;re a little bit the same and a little bit different to other girls. I think Rainbows learn more things. I think it&amp;rsquo;s easier than at school because there are no boys.&amp;rdquo; &lt;small&gt;Isha, 6&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;The best bit was the party for my Promise because we all ate chocolate cake!&amp;rdquo; &lt;small&gt;Louise, 5&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;


 

	 
	 
		
		&lt;div class=&#34;panel panel-default&#34;&gt;
			&lt;div class=&#34;panel-heading&#34;&gt;
				&lt;a data-toggle=&#34;collapse&#34; data-target=&#34;#collapserainbows&#34; class=&#34;collapsea&#34;&gt;&lt;div style=&#34;width:100%&#34;&gt;Our Rainbows groups &lt;span class=&#34;glyphicon glyphicon-menu-down&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;div class=&#34;panel-collapse collapse&#34; id=&#34;collapserainbows&#34;&gt;
				&lt;div class=&#34;table-responsive&#34;&gt;
					&lt;table class=&#34;table table-striped table-hover&#34;&gt;
						&lt;thead&gt;
							&lt;tr&gt;
								&lt;th&gt;Unit&lt;/th&gt;
								&lt;th&gt;Meets on&lt;/th&gt;
								&lt;th&gt;Spaces Available?&lt;/th&gt;
							&lt;/tr&gt;
						&lt;/thead&gt;
						&lt;tbody&gt;
						
							&lt;tr&gt;
								&lt;td&gt;5th Beeston Rainbows&lt;/td&gt;
								&lt;td&gt;Mondays&lt;/td&gt;
								&lt;td  class=&#34;success&#34;  &gt; Yes &lt;/td&gt;
							&lt;/tr&gt;
						
							&lt;tr&gt;
								&lt;td&gt;2nd Beeston Rainbows&lt;/td&gt;
								&lt;td&gt;Wednesdays&lt;/td&gt;
								&lt;td  class=&#34;success&#34;  &gt; Yes &lt;/td&gt;
							&lt;/tr&gt;
						
							&lt;tr&gt;
								&lt;td&gt;6th Beeston Rainbows&lt;/td&gt;
								&lt;td&gt;Thursdays&lt;/td&gt;
								&lt;td  class=&#34;success&#34;  &gt; Yes &lt;/td&gt;
							&lt;/tr&gt;
						
							&lt;tr&gt;
								&lt;td&gt;4th Chilwell Rainbows&lt;/td&gt;
								&lt;td&gt;Thursdays&lt;/td&gt;
								&lt;td  class=&#34;success&#34;  &gt; Yes &lt;/td&gt;
							&lt;/tr&gt;
						
						&lt;/tbody&gt;
					&lt;/table&gt;
				&lt;/div&gt;
				&lt;div class=&#34;panel-footer&#34;&gt;
					&lt;p&gt;If the group you&#39;re looking to join has no spaces available, please contact us to join the waiting list.&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	



&lt;h1 id=&#34;brownies&#34;&gt;Brownies&lt;/h1&gt;



  
  
      
    
      
    
  
  
  
   
  
   

   
  
 	&lt;p class=&#34;pullquote pullquote-center&#34; data-pullquote=&#34;Brownies do it all!&#34;&gt;
 	&lt;hr class=&#34;pullquote-center&#34;&gt;
  	 
	&lt;/p&gt;
  



&lt;p&gt;Their meetings are full of challenges, games and activities, usually ones that the Brownies have suggested themselves. Brownies are girls aged 7 to 10.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Brownies follow a programme called the &lt;strong&gt;Brownie Adventure&lt;/strong&gt;. The name reflects the world of exciting opportunities, challenges and fun that is Brownies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Girls can participate in a wide range of activities at their regular meetings, and at special events, day trips, sleepovers, camps and holidays. They can find themselves trying out arts and crafts or recipes, playing energetic games, taking part in community action projects, or zooming down zip wires at one of our activity centres.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Girls can also extend their knowledge and abilities by working towards Brownies interest badges covering many different hobbies and activities from Science Investigator to Circus Skills.
The Brownie Adventure is divided into three areas: &lt;em&gt;You, Community, World&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;We ate apples and honey, which actually tasted really nice!&amp;rdquo; &lt;small&gt;Sana, 8&lt;/small&gt;
&amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m doing my Out and about and Science investigator badges – I&amp;rsquo;m learning to use maps and I&amp;rsquo;m doing lots of cool science investigations. I want to do my Water sports badge next.&amp;rdquo; &lt;small&gt;Chloe, 9&lt;/small&gt;
&amp;ldquo;It feels nice to be part of a group of girls who help each other and are friendly. It makes me feel special. I&amp;rsquo;d hate there to be boys at Brownies!&amp;rdquo; &lt;small&gt;Heather, 10&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;


 

	 
	 
		
		&lt;div class=&#34;panel panel-default&#34;&gt;
			&lt;div class=&#34;panel-heading&#34;&gt;
				&lt;a data-toggle=&#34;collapse&#34; data-target=&#34;#collapsebrownies&#34; class=&#34;collapsea&#34;&gt;&lt;div style=&#34;width:100%&#34;&gt;Our Brownies groups &lt;span class=&#34;glyphicon glyphicon-menu-down&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;div class=&#34;panel-collapse collapse&#34; id=&#34;collapsebrownies&#34;&gt;
				&lt;div class=&#34;table-responsive&#34;&gt;
					&lt;table class=&#34;table table-striped table-hover&#34;&gt;
						&lt;thead&gt;
							&lt;tr&gt;
								&lt;th&gt;Unit&lt;/th&gt;
								&lt;th&gt;Meets on&lt;/th&gt;
								&lt;th&gt;Spaces Available?&lt;/th&gt;
							&lt;/tr&gt;
						&lt;/thead&gt;
						&lt;tbody&gt;
						
							&lt;tr&gt;
								&lt;td&gt;5th Beeston Brownies&lt;/td&gt;
								&lt;td&gt;Mondays&lt;/td&gt;
								&lt;td  class=&#34;success&#34;  &gt; Yes &lt;/td&gt;
							&lt;/tr&gt;
						
							&lt;tr&gt;
								&lt;td&gt;6th Beeston Brownies&lt;/td&gt;
								&lt;td&gt;Wednesdays&lt;/td&gt;
								&lt;td  class=&#34;success&#34;  &gt; Yes &lt;/td&gt;
							&lt;/tr&gt;
						
							&lt;tr&gt;
								&lt;td&gt;1st Beeston Brownies&lt;/td&gt;
								&lt;td&gt;Thursdays&lt;/td&gt;
								&lt;td  class=&#34;success&#34;  &gt; Yes &lt;/td&gt;
							&lt;/tr&gt;
						
							&lt;tr&gt;
								&lt;td&gt;4th Beeston Brownies&lt;/td&gt;
								&lt;td&gt;Thursdays&lt;/td&gt;
								&lt;td  class=&#34;success&#34;  &gt; Yes &lt;/td&gt;
							&lt;/tr&gt;
						
							&lt;tr&gt;
								&lt;td&gt;1st Chilwell Brownies&lt;/td&gt;
								&lt;td&gt;Fridays&lt;/td&gt;
								&lt;td  class=&#34;danger&#34;  &gt; No &lt;/td&gt;
							&lt;/tr&gt;
						
							&lt;tr&gt;
								&lt;td&gt;4th Chilwell Brownies&lt;/td&gt;
								&lt;td&gt;Fridays&lt;/td&gt;
								&lt;td  class=&#34;success&#34;  &gt; Yes &lt;/td&gt;
							&lt;/tr&gt;
						
						&lt;/tbody&gt;
					&lt;/table&gt;
				&lt;/div&gt;
				&lt;div class=&#34;panel-footer&#34;&gt;
					&lt;p&gt;If the group you&#39;re looking to join has no spaces available, please contact us to join the waiting list.&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	



&lt;h1 id=&#34;guides&#34;&gt;Guides&lt;/h1&gt;



  
  
      
    
      
    
  
  
  
   
  
   

   
  
 	&lt;p class=&#34;pullquote pullquote-center&#34; data-pullquote=&#34;Guides go for it!&#34;&gt;
 	&lt;hr class=&#34;pullquote-center&#34;&gt;
  	 
	&lt;/p&gt;
  



&lt;p&gt;Being a Guide encourages girls to develop by undertaking challenges and pushing the boundaries of their experience. Guides are girls aged 10 to 14.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Members take part in a wide range of exciting activities at their regular meetings, and at special events or holidays.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Girls do everything from adventure sports to playing fun games, and from taking part in community action projects to the performing arts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Guides work together in small groups or &amp;lsquo;Patrols&amp;rsquo; and, with the support of an adult Leader, choose and run some of the activities themselves using &lt;em&gt;Go for It!&lt;/em&gt; resource packs.
&lt;div class=&#34;row&#34;&gt;
	


 
  
	
		&lt;div class=&#34;col-sm-6&#34;&gt; 
			Girls can extend their knowledge and skills by working towards Guide interest badges covering many different hobbies and activities from Film lover to Independent living. They can also gain Challenge badges that recognise their participation in Girlguiding over a period of time. The badges build towards the Baden-Powell Challenge Award, named in honour of the founder of Girlguiding.
		&lt;/div&gt;




 
  
	
		&lt;div class=&#34;col-sm-6&#34;&gt; 
			The Guide programme is divided into five areas:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;discovery of new experiences and challenges&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;healthy lifestyles&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;global awareness&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;skills and relationships&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;celebrating diversity.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

		&lt;/div&gt;



&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Because of guiding I&amp;rsquo;m a lot more confident meeting new people. And I&amp;rsquo;ve got a really diverse bunch of friends because of it too.&amp;rdquo; &lt;small&gt;Megan, 20&lt;/small&gt;
&amp;ldquo;Guiding lets girls think, learn and develop without having to put up with boys trying to be the centre of attention all the time!&amp;rdquo; &lt;small&gt;Philippa, 16&lt;/small&gt;
&amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;ve had amazing experiences no other organisation can offer.  And we really do get to have our say in stuff that matters.&amp;rdquo; &lt;small&gt;Lucy, 23&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;


 

	 
	 
		
		&lt;div class=&#34;panel panel-default&#34;&gt;
			&lt;div class=&#34;panel-heading&#34;&gt;
				&lt;a data-toggle=&#34;collapse&#34; data-target=&#34;#collapseguides&#34; class=&#34;collapsea&#34;&gt;&lt;div style=&#34;width:100%&#34;&gt;Our Guides groups &lt;span class=&#34;glyphicon glyphicon-menu-down&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;div class=&#34;panel-collapse collapse&#34; id=&#34;collapseguides&#34;&gt;
				&lt;div class=&#34;table-responsive&#34;&gt;
					&lt;table class=&#34;table table-striped table-hover&#34;&gt;
						&lt;thead&gt;
							&lt;tr&gt;
								&lt;th&gt;Unit&lt;/th&gt;
								&lt;th&gt;Meets on&lt;/th&gt;
								&lt;th&gt;Spaces Available?&lt;/th&gt;
							&lt;/tr&gt;
						&lt;/thead&gt;
						&lt;tbody&gt;
						
							&lt;tr&gt;
								&lt;td&gt;5th Beeston Guides&lt;/td&gt;
								&lt;td&gt;Mondays&lt;/td&gt;
								&lt;td  class=&#34;danger&#34;  &gt; No &lt;/td&gt;
							&lt;/tr&gt;
						
							&lt;tr&gt;
								&lt;td&gt;6th Beeston Guides&lt;/td&gt;
								&lt;td&gt;Tuesdays&lt;/td&gt;
								&lt;td  class=&#34;danger&#34;  &gt; No &lt;/td&gt;
							&lt;/tr&gt;
						
							&lt;tr&gt;
								&lt;td&gt;2nd Beeston Guides&lt;/td&gt;
								&lt;td&gt;Thursdays&lt;/td&gt;
								&lt;td  class=&#34;success&#34;  &gt; Yes &lt;/td&gt;
							&lt;/tr&gt;
						
							&lt;tr&gt;
								&lt;td&gt;1st Chilwell Guides&lt;/td&gt;
								&lt;td&gt;Fridays&lt;/td&gt;
								&lt;td  class=&#34;success&#34;  &gt; Yes &lt;/td&gt;
							&lt;/tr&gt;
						
						&lt;/tbody&gt;
					&lt;/table&gt;
				&lt;/div&gt;
				&lt;div class=&#34;panel-footer&#34;&gt;
					&lt;p&gt;If the group you&#39;re looking to join has no spaces available, please contact us to join the waiting list.&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	



&lt;h1 id=&#34;senior-section&#34;&gt;Senior Section&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Senior Section is for young women aged 14 to 25. It offers an exciting and flexible programme with a huge variety of challenges and opportunities for personal development – sure to impress universities and potential employers!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Look Wider programme offers a range of activities and challenges and motivates members to try out new things – it could be learning a language, playing a musical instrument, running a marathon, camping in the wilds or volunteering overseas. It is flexible and participants can take their chosen activities as far as they wish, from taster level all the way to gaining a qualification that is recognised outside Girlguiding.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Senior Section members can undertake a wide range of awards and qualifications. These include: the Young Leader qualification, which allows them to aid in the running of units for younger girls; the internationally-recognised Duke of Edinburgh&amp;rsquo;s Award Scheme; and other prestigious awards unique to Girlguiding.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are multiple other activities open to Senior Section members. They can do anything from speaking to younger units about current issues as a peer educator, to changing the future of Girlguiding at an Innovate meeting, to volunteering on an international community project.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Because of guiding I&amp;rsquo;m a lot more confident meeting new people. And I&amp;rsquo;ve got a really diverse bunch of friends because of it too.&amp;rdquo; &lt;small&gt;Megan, 20&lt;/small&gt;
&amp;ldquo;Guiding lets girls think, learn and develop without having to put up with boys trying to be the centre of attention all the time!&amp;rdquo; &lt;small&gt;Philippa, 16&lt;/small&gt;
&amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;ve had amazing experiences no other organisation can offer.  And we really do get to have our say in stuff that matters.&amp;rdquo; &lt;small&gt;Lucy, 23&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;


 

	 
	 
		
		&lt;div class=&#34;panel panel-default&#34;&gt;
			&lt;div class=&#34;panel-heading&#34;&gt;
				&lt;a data-toggle=&#34;collapse&#34; data-target=&#34;#collapsesenior-section&#34; class=&#34;collapsea&#34;&gt;&lt;div style=&#34;width:100%&#34;&gt;Our Senior Section groups &lt;span class=&#34;glyphicon glyphicon-menu-down&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;div class=&#34;panel-collapse collapse&#34; id=&#34;collapsesenior-section&#34;&gt;
				&lt;div class=&#34;table-responsive&#34;&gt;
					&lt;table class=&#34;table table-striped table-hover&#34;&gt;
						&lt;thead&gt;
							&lt;tr&gt;
								&lt;th&gt;Unit&lt;/th&gt;
								&lt;th&gt;Meets on&lt;/th&gt;
								&lt;th&gt;Spaces Available?&lt;/th&gt;
							&lt;/tr&gt;
						&lt;/thead&gt;
						&lt;tbody&gt;
						
							&lt;tr&gt;
								&lt;td&gt;Beeston and Chilwell Senior Section&lt;/td&gt;
								&lt;td&gt;Thursdays&lt;/td&gt;
								&lt;td  class=&#34;warning&#34;  &gt; Unknown &lt;/td&gt;
							&lt;/tr&gt;
						
						&lt;/tbody&gt;
					&lt;/table&gt;
				&lt;/div&gt;
				&lt;div class=&#34;panel-footer&#34;&gt;
					&lt;p&gt;If the group you&#39;re looking to join has no spaces available, please contact us to join the waiting list.&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	


</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Beeston Guides</title>
      <link>http://samozzy.github.io/guides/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2016 01:16:28 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://samozzy.github.io/guides/about/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;about-girlguiding&#34;&gt;About Girlguiding&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Girlguiding was founded in 1910 by Robert and Agnes Baden-Powell, and has been running successfully ever since. By the end of 2013, Girlguiding UK had over 553,000 members throughout its many divisions and groups. Estimates suggest that around 1 in 4 of 8-year-old girls in the UK are involved in guiding.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our younger groups, Brownies (previously known as Rosebuds) and Rainbows were formed in 1914 and 1987 respectively. The Trefoil Guild was formed for any members over 18 who wished to remain a part of Girlguiding but couldn&amp;rsquo;t remain active within a unit in 1943.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;promise&#34;&gt;Promise&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Upon joining, all members of Girlguiding make a promise:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I promise that I will do my best;&lt;br /&gt;
To be true to myself and develop my beliefs,&lt;br /&gt;
To serve the Queen and my community,&lt;br /&gt;
To help other people and&lt;br /&gt;
To keep the (Brownie) Guide Law.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For Rainbows, the promise is a little different:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I promise that I will do my best&lt;br /&gt;
to think about my beliefs&lt;br /&gt;
and to be kind and helpful&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;beyond-the-uk&#34;&gt;Beyond the UK&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Girlguiding isn&amp;rsquo;t just unique to the UK. There are Girlguiding Associations in nine international locations: Anguilla, Bermuda, British Virgin Islands, Cayman Islands, Falkland Islands, Gibraltar, Montserrat, Saint Helena and the Turks &amp;amp; Caicos Islands.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;More information about our international friends can be found at &lt;a href=&#34;http://girlguiding-bam.org&#34;&gt;The Branch Association Members website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;more-information&#34;&gt;More information&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To find out more about Girlguiding in both Nottinghamshire and the UK, please visit the &lt;a href=&#34;http://girlguidingnottinghamshire.org.uk&#34;&gt;Girlguiding Nottinghamshire&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;http://girlguiding.org.uk&#34;&gt;Girlguiding UK&lt;/a&gt; websites.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beeston HQ</title>
      <link>http://samozzy.github.io/guides/venue/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2016 15:46:07 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://samozzy.github.io/guides/venue/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;location&#34;&gt;Location&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;row&#34;&gt;
	


 
  
	
		&lt;div class=&#34;col-sm-6&#34;&gt; 
			&lt;div id=&#34;map&#34; style=&#34;height:300px&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

		&lt;/div&gt;




 
  
	
		&lt;div class=&#34;col-sm-6&#34;&gt; 
			All of our Beeston-based meetings take place at Beeston HQ, our Girlguiding venue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Address&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Beeston HQ,&lt;br /&gt;
Beeston Youth and Community Centre,&lt;br /&gt;
West End,&lt;br /&gt;
Beeston,&lt;br /&gt;
NG9 1GL
		&lt;/div&gt;



&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;getting-here&#34;&gt;Getting Here&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;row&#34;&gt;
	



 
  
	
		&lt;div class=&#34;col-sm-4&#34;&gt; 
			&lt;h3 id=&#34;i-class-fa-fa-car-i-by-road&#34;&gt;&lt;i class=&#34;fa fa-car&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt; By road&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Via the M1, get off on Junction 25 and follow signs towards Beeston via the A52 (Brian Clough Way)
		&lt;/div&gt;





 
  
	
		&lt;div class=&#34;col-sm-4&#34;&gt; 
			&lt;h3 id=&#34;i-class-fa-fa-train-i-by-train&#34;&gt;&lt;i class=&#34;fa fa-train&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt; By train&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beeston HQ is around a 10-15 minute walk from Beeston train station, which is easily accessible from Nottingham station, with trains running every 30-60 minutes.
		&lt;/div&gt;





 
  
	
		&lt;div class=&#34;col-sm-4&#34;&gt; 
			&lt;h3 id=&#34;i-class-fa-fa-bus-i-by-bus&#34;&gt;&lt;i class=&#34;fa fa-bus&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt; By bus&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We recommend catching one of the many buses to Beeston Interchange and then following the &amp;lsquo;on foot&amp;rsquo; directions.
Buses calling at Beeston Interchange include the Indigo, 18, Skylink, Y5, Y36 and 36B.
		&lt;/div&gt;



&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;row&#34;&gt;
	


 
  
	
		&lt;div class=&#34;col-sm-4&#34;&gt; 
			&lt;h3 id=&#34;i-class-fa-fa-subway-i-by-tram&#34;&gt;&lt;i class=&#34;fa fa-subway&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt; By tram&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The nearest tram stop is Beeston Centre (also known as Beeston Interchange), and trams run up to every 10 minutes during peak times.
		&lt;/div&gt;





 
  
	
		&lt;div class=&#34;col-sm-4&#34;&gt; 
			&lt;h3 id=&#34;i-class-fa-fa-male-i-by-foot&#34;&gt;&lt;i class=&#34;fa fa-male&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt; By foot&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From Beeston Centre, or the Beeston Interchange, head towards the Scout Centre, and then follow directions for Beeston Community Centre, which will take you up West End. We&amp;rsquo;re approx. 10 minutes&amp;rsquo; walk from Beeston Interchange.
		&lt;/div&gt;



&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;hire&#34;&gt;Hire&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;row&#34;&gt;
	


 
  
	
		&lt;div class=&#34;col-sm-6&#34;&gt; 
			&lt;small&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;panel panel-primary&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;panel-heading&#34;&gt;Specification&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;ul class=&#34;list-group&#34;&gt;
        &lt;li class=&#34;list-group-item&#34;&gt;
            Dimensions: 10.2m x 8.1m (34&amp;rsquo; x 27&amp;rsquo;)
        &lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li class=&#34;list-group-item&#34;&gt;
            Hearing loop system fitted
        &lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li class=&#34;list-group-item&#34;&gt;
            &lt;strong&gt;Fully equipped kitchen&lt;/strong&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;Dimensions: 4.8m x 3.9m (16&amp;rsquo; x 13&amp;rsquo;). Includes fridge, freezer, microwave, tumble dryer, and double electric oven with five halogen rings.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li class=&#34;list-group-item&#34;&gt;
            Toilets and washroom, plus one fully accessible toilet and shower.
        &lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li class=&#34;list-group-item&#34;&gt;
            Small grassed area, as well as a large park within walking distance.
        &lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li class=&#34;list-group-item&#34;&gt;
            &lt;strong&gt;Additional&lt;/strong&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;PA System&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Projector and screen&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
        &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/small&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;




 
  
	
		&lt;div class=&#34;col-sm-6&#34;&gt; 
			By hiring our venue, you can hold your event here and take use of our great facilities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For events at any time - daytime or evening - the capacity of 100 means Beeston HQ is great for most small events.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beeston HQ is fully accessible, competitively priced, and the site is fully secured.
		&lt;/div&gt;



&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more information please contact Pete Treagus or Kaye Ford the bookings secretary.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;amenities&#34;&gt;Amenities&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Being situated just outside Beeston provides easy access to the local facilities, such as supermarkets, post office, banks and assorted shops.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A 10 minute walk to the nearby bus station provides access to Nottingham, Bramcote (offering a leisure center), and places further afield such as Derby.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The nearby train station offers services to Nottingham and Derby directly, providing the city amenities and opportunities to travel further.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact Us</title>
      <link>http://samozzy.github.io/guides/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2016 15:46:07 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://samozzy.github.io/guides/contact/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Whether you or your daughter want to join us, or you&amp;rsquo;d just like to know more about our division, just drop us a line below and we&amp;rsquo;ll get back to you as soon as possible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Alternatively, you can contact one of &lt;a href=&#34;http://samozzy.github.io/guides/guides/team/&#34;&gt;the team&lt;/a&gt;, or message us on Facebook.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any suggestions for this website, put &lt;code&gt;Website:&lt;/code&gt; as the subject.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;contact-form&#34;&gt;Contact form&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;col-xs-12&#34;&gt;
	&lt;form name=&#34;contactForm&#34; id=&#34;contactForm&#34; novalidate&gt; 
		&lt;div class=&#34;row control-group&#34;&gt;
			&lt;div class=&#34;col-xs-12 floating-label-form-group form-group controls&#34;&gt;
				&lt;label&gt;Your Name&lt;/label&gt;
				&lt;input class=&#34;form-control&#34; type=&#34;text&#34; name=&#34;name&#34; placeholder=&#34;Your Name&#34; id=&#34;name&#34; required data-validation-required-message=&#34;Please enter your name.&#34;&gt;
				&lt;p class=&#34;help-block bg-danger&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;div class=&#34;row control-group&#34;&gt;
			&lt;div class=&#34;col-xs-12 floating-label-form-group form-group controls&#34;&gt;
				&lt;label&gt;Email Address&lt;/label&gt;
				&lt;input class=&#34;form-control&#34; type=&#34;email&#34; placeholder=&#34;Your email address&#34; name=&#34;_replyto&#34; id=&#34;email&#34; required data-validation-required-message=&#34;Please enter a valid email address&#34;&gt;
				&lt;p class=&#34;help-block bg-danger&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;div class=&#34;row control-group&#34;&gt;
			&lt;div class=&#34;col-xs-12 floating-label-form-group form-group controls&#34;&gt;
				&lt;label&gt;Subject&lt;/label&gt;
				&lt;input class=&#34;form-control&#34; type=&#34;text&#34; name=&#34;_subject&#34; placeholder=&#34;Subject&#34; id=&#34;subject&#34; required data-validation-required-message=&#34;Please enter a subject.&#34;&gt;
				&lt;p class=&#34;help-block bg-danger&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;div class=&#34;row control-group&#34;&gt;
			&lt;div class=&#34;col-xs-12 floating-label-form-group form-group controls&#34;&gt;
				&lt;label&gt;Your message&lt;/label&gt;
				&lt;textarea rows=&#34;4&#34; class=&#34;form-control&#34; placeholder=&#34;Message&#34; name=&#34;message&#34; id=&#34;message&#34; required data-validation-required-message=&#34;Please enter a message&#34;&gt;&lt;/textarea&gt;
				&lt;p class=&#34;help-block bg-danger&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;br /&gt;
		&lt;div id=&#34;success&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;div class=&#34;row&#34;&gt;
			&lt;div class=&#34;col-xs-8 form-group&#34;&gt;
				&lt;button type=&#34;submit&#34; name=&#34;submit&#34; class=&#34;btn btn-lg btn-primary&#34;&gt;Submit&lt;/button&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/form&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rainbows Go Climbing!</title>
      <link>http://samozzy.github.io/guides/news/climbing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://samozzy.github.io/guides/news/climbing/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;On 4th July, 10 of our Rainbows visited the Depot climbing center in Nottingham City Centre. After a short tram journey, we arrived at the center and found our shoes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our instructor helped us do some warm-up activities and games before we took to the wall after a short safety demonstration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All of our Rainbows had a great time, and I think we&amp;rsquo;ve got some junior climbers in our midst! There was even a chance for our Leaders to take a climb.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We finished with our instructor playing some warm-down games, which everyone found to be a very enjoyable end of a fabulous evening out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My favourite part was the shark attack game at the end! &amp;ndash; Jessica&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Hartley good jam</title>
      <link>http://samozzy.github.io/guides/news/jam/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://samozzy.github.io/guides/news/jam/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It was the 27th May, the strawberries were ripening on their branches, and the jars were ready. All signs pointing to a fun afternoon of jam-making!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;

  
  
      
    
      
    
  
  
  
   
  
   

   
  
 	&lt;p class=&#34;pullquote pullquote-right&#34; data-pullquote=&#34;&amp;#34;I think I know what&amp;#39;s going in my sandwiches for tomorrow&amp;#39;s packed lunch!&amp;#34; - Hayley&#34;&gt;
 	&lt;hr class=&#34;pullquote-right&#34;&gt;
  	 
	&lt;/p&gt;
  


The Brownies arrived, punnets and empty jars in hand, and we cracked on. After the fun of crushing and sieving the strawberries, the girls were supervised as they came to the boil. Adding sugar and some water, we sat and waited while the fruits of our labour were revealed to us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And fruity it was! No fewer than 15 jars of jam were collected from the Brownie fridge on this Friday afternoon, and each more tempting as the last.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Tower of Love</title>
      <link>http://samozzy.github.io/guides/news/hearts-tower/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://samozzy.github.io/guides/news/hearts-tower/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;On 1st February, calm took over the centre as 1st Chilwell Brownies took to their tables.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In teams of four, the packets of Love Hearts were opened, decanted into bowls, and tower-making began.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The concentration on each of their faces was rich as the clock ticked by; each group fearing the worst - a collapse.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No such disaster occurred, as each group built a successful tower of love hearts to show off at the end of the session.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The best part was that, at the end, we could take it all apart and eat it!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>