<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>News-rsses on Girlguiding Beeston and Chilwell</title>
    <link>http://guides.samosborne.me/news/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in News-rsses on Girlguiding Beeston and Chilwell</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2016 Girlguiding</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://guides.samosborne.me/news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Rainbows Go Climbing!</title>
      <link>http://guides.samosborne.me/news/climbing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://guides.samosborne.me/news/climbing/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;On 4th July, 10 of our Rainbows visited the Depot climbing center in Nottingham City Centre. After a short tram journey, we arrived at the center and found our shoes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our instructor helped us do some warm-up activities and games before we took to the wall after a short safety demonstration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All of our Rainbows had a great time, and I think we&amp;rsquo;ve got some junior climbers in our midst! There was even a chance for our Leaders to take a climb.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We finished with our instructor playing some warm-down games, which everyone found to be a very enjoyable end of a fabulous evening out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My favourite part was the shark attack game at the end! &amp;ndash; Jessica&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Hartley good jam</title>
      <link>http://guides.samosborne.me/news/jam/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://guides.samosborne.me/news/jam/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It was the 27th May, the strawberries were ripening on their branches, and the jars were ready. All signs pointing to a fun afternoon of jam-making!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;

  
  
      
    
      
    
  
  
  
   
  
   

   
  
 	&lt;p class=&#34;pullquote pullquote-right&#34; data-pullquote=&#34;&amp;#34;I think I know what&amp;#39;s going in my sandwiches for tomorrow&amp;#39;s packed lunch!&amp;#34; - Hayley&#34;&gt;
 	&lt;hr class=&#34;pullquote-right&#34;&gt;
  	 
	&lt;/p&gt;
  


The Brownies arrived, punnets and empty jars in hand, and we cracked on. After the fun of crushing and sieving the strawberries, the girls were supervised as they came to the boil. Adding sugar and some water, we sat and waited while the fruits of our labour were revealed to us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And fruity it was! No fewer than 15 jars of jam were collected from the Brownie fridge on this Friday afternoon, and each more tempting as the last.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Tower of Love</title>
      <link>http://guides.samosborne.me/news/hearts-tower/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://guides.samosborne.me/news/hearts-tower/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;On 1st February, calm took over the centre as 1st Chilwell Brownies took to their tables.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In teams of four, the packets of Love Hearts were opened, decanted into bowls, and tower-making began.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The concentration on each of their faces was rich as the clock ticked by; each group fearing the worst - a collapse.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No such disaster occurred, as each group built a successful tower of love hearts to show off at the end of the session.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The best part was that, at the end, we could take it all apart and eat it!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>