<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Homepage-rsses on Girlguiding Beeston and Chilwell</title>
    <link>https://samozzy.github.io/guides/homepage/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Homepage-rsses on Girlguiding Beeston and Chilwell</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2016 Girlguiding</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2016 00:02:48 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://samozzy.github.io/guides/homepage/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>1</title>
      <link>https://samozzy.github.io/guides/homepage/1%20-%20Intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2016 00:02:48 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samozzy.github.io/guides/homepage/1%20-%20Intro/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;text-center&#34;&gt;
 &lt;h1 id=&#34;girlguiding-opens-a-world-of-opportunities-that-will-last-a-lifetime&#34;&gt;Girlguiding opens a world of opportunities that will last a lifetime&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beeston and Chilwell Division has over 330 members across 15 groups across all of Beeston and Chilwell. Our members are of all ages, spanning our Rainbows, Brownies, Guides, Senior Section and adult volunteers - including many students from the University of Nottingham.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Being a member of Girlguiding opens a world of opportunities that will last a lifetime. It provides a safe, girl-only space to explore activities, issues and possibilities that are available to girls today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are a friendly, forward looking division and our aim is to provide the best guiding and life opportunities for all our members. This is made possible by the enthusiasm and efforts of our many volunteers – no contribution is too small.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5</title>
      <link>https://samozzy.github.io/guides/homepage/5%20-%20Volunteers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2016 23:50:01 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samozzy.github.io/guides/homepage/5%20-%20Volunteers/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;volunteers-make-guiding-happen&#34;&gt;Volunteers make Guiding happen&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Enthusiasm, common sense and a friendly approach are all that’s needed. As a volunteer with Girlguiding, you&amp;rsquo;ll make new friends, have a good time and make a real difference to the lives of today&amp;rsquo;s girls and young women. Beeston and Chilwell Division Rainbows, Brownies and Guides need you! Lots of girls are waiting but we need leaders and helpers to get them in on all the fun.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Opportunities exist on different evenings throughout Beeston and Chilwell, with full support and training available. Flexible volunteering makes it easy for people to share skills, time and energy in a way that suits their lifestyle.&lt;/p&gt;


 

	 
	
		
	
		
	
		
	
		
			&lt;div class=&#34;row text-left&#34;&gt; 
				&lt;div class=&#34;col-md-8 col-md-offset-2 col-xs-12&#34;&gt;
					&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;h3&gt;After studying English at university, I decided I wanted to teach. My experience within guiding helped me to gain a place on one of the best teaching courses and now I am teaching English to Guide age and above! &lt;small&gt;Komal, Girlguiding Beeston Leader&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
				&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
		
	

</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4</title>
      <link>https://samozzy.github.io/guides/homepage/4%20-%20Adults/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2016 23:49:45 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samozzy.github.io/guides/homepage/4%20-%20Adults/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;adults&#34;&gt;Adults&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Girlguiding isn&amp;rsquo;t just for girls - within Beeston and Chilwell Division, there are over 80 adult volunteers. Many amazing volunteers contribute time to guiding every year. In return, we offer training and the opportunity to develop new skills.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are many volunteer roles in guiding. Many volunteers give their time as Leaders or Assistant Leaders for guiding units and get to see girls enjoying events and activities that they have organised. Other volunteers take on administrative responsibilities, or help out with driving or maintenance on an occasional basis.&lt;/p&gt;


 

	 
	
		
	
		
	
		
			&lt;div class=&#34;row text-left&#34;&gt; 
				&lt;div class=&#34;col-md-8 col-md-offset-2 col-xs-12&#34;&gt;
					&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Guiding has helped me become the person I am today, which is a confident and outspoken girl! &lt;small&gt;Dawn, 17&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
				&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
		
	
		
	

</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2</title>
      <link>https://samozzy.github.io/guides/homepage/2%20-%20We%20Do/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2016 20:00:51 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samozzy.github.io/guides/homepage/2%20-%20We%20Do/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;row&#34;&gt;
	


 
  
	
		&lt;div class=&#34;col-sm-4&#34;&gt; 
			&lt;h2 id=&#34;we-provide-girls-their-own-space&#34;&gt;We provide girls their own space&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We give girls a place where they can really be themselves with other girls and share the experience of growing up as a girl in today’s world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We provide a safe, non-judgemental environment where girls can explore the issues they care about while having lots of fun, enjoying new experiences and learning vital skills.
		&lt;/div&gt;




 
  
	
		&lt;div class=&#34;col-sm-4&#34;&gt; 
			&lt;h2 id=&#34;we-are-for-all-girls&#34;&gt;We are for all girls&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are for all girls and young women, whatever their background and circumstances. We offer them fun, exciting activities and the chance to make lifelong friends.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’ll find us in many communities, helping to give girls a head start in life and encouraging them to be happy, self-confident and curious about the world they live in and the difference they can make.
		&lt;/div&gt;




 
  
	
		&lt;div class=&#34;col-sm-4&#34;&gt; 
			&lt;h2 id=&#34;we-give-girls-a-voice&#34;&gt;We give girls a voice&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We give girls the confidence, skills and information to make informed decisions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We offer a supportive, inclusive and exciting environment where they can reach their own conclusions about the world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We show them how they can speak out and take positive action to improve their lives and the lives of others.
		&lt;/div&gt;



&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
 

	 
	
		
			&lt;div class=&#34;row text-left&#34;&gt; 
				&lt;div class=&#34;col-md-8 col-md-offset-2 col-xs-12&#34;&gt;
					&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;h3&gt;We play games, we celebrate things, we write in our books, we play on the computer, we do painting… &lt;small&gt;Fareeha, 6&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
				&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
		
	
		
	
		
	
		
	
&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3</title>
      <link>https://samozzy.github.io/guides/homepage/3%20-%20Our%20Groups/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2016 20:00:51 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samozzy.github.io/guides/homepage/3%20-%20Our%20Groups/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;our-groups&#34;&gt;Our groups&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
 

	 
	
	   
	    &lt;div class=&#34;col-md-3 col-sm-6&#34;&gt;
	      &lt;h3&gt;Rainbows&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://samozzy.github.io/guides/guides/groups/#rainbows&#39;&gt;&lt;button class=&#34;btn btn-primary&#34;&gt;Read more...&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
	      &lt;p&gt;Girlguiding starts aged 5 with our youngest group. Rainbows play games, have parties, make things and enjoy the outdoors while developing life skills.&lt;/p&gt;
	    &lt;/div&gt;
	  
  


 

	 
	
	   
	    &lt;div class=&#34;col-md-3 col-sm-6&#34;&gt;
	      &lt;h3&gt;Brownies&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://samozzy.github.io/guides/guides/groups/#brownies&#39;&gt;&lt;button class=&#34;btn btn-primary&#34;&gt;Read more...&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
	      &lt;p&gt;Brownies do it all! From ages 7-10, Brownies make up and take on their own challenges, as well as playing fun games.&lt;/p&gt;
	    &lt;/div&gt;
	  
  


 

	 
	
	   
	    &lt;div class=&#34;col-md-3 col-sm-6&#34;&gt;
	      &lt;h3&gt;Guides&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://samozzy.github.io/guides/guides/groups/#guides&#39;&gt;&lt;button class=&#34;btn btn-primary&#34;&gt;Read more...&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
	      &lt;p&gt;Being a Guide encourages girls aged 10-14 to develop by undertaking challenges and pushing the boundaries of their experience.&lt;/p&gt;
	    &lt;/div&gt;
	  
  


 

	 
	
	   
	    &lt;div class=&#34;col-md-3 col-sm-6&#34;&gt;
	      &lt;h3&gt;Senior Section&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://samozzy.github.io/guides/guides/groups/#senior-section&#39;&gt;&lt;button class=&#34;btn btn-primary&#34;&gt;Read more...&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
	      &lt;p&gt;For anyone 14-25, the Senior Section offers young women an exciting and flexible programme with a huge variety of challenges and opportunities for personal development.&lt;/p&gt;
	    &lt;/div&gt;
	  
  
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
 

	 
	
		
	
		
			&lt;div class=&#34;row text-left&#34;&gt; 
				&lt;div class=&#34;col-md-8 col-md-offset-2 col-xs-12&#34;&gt;
					&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;h3&gt;It feels nice to be part of a group of girls who help each other and are friendly. It makes me feel special. I&amp;#39;d hate there to be boys at Brownies! &lt;small&gt;Heather, 10&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
				&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
		
	
		
	
		
	
&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>